Atmospheric Sciences and Research Center; Records ua450
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1961-1992; 3; 5.5 cubic ft.
  - Experiments with Aitken Conters in Maritime Atmosphere- A.W. Hogan, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 76)
  - Water Pollution by Outbound Motors- Ronald Stewart, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 77)
  - On the Nature of Tropospheric Ions- Volker Mohnen, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 78)
  - A Self-Energizing Corona Current Meter- R.A. Cudney & C.T. Phelps, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 79)
  - General Purpose Gas Sampling Tube- Earl N. & F. Norton, 1968 September (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 80)
  - Windchill, A Useful Wintertime Weather Variable- Raymond Falconer, 1968 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 81)
  - Final Report of the Natural Sciences Insitute for the years 1966-1968, 1968 September (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 82)
  - What About the Next Twenty Years - V.J. Schaefer, 1968 June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 83)
  - Fog Modification with Giant Hygroscopic Nuclei- J.E. Juisto, R.J. Pilie, W.C. Kocmond, 1968 October 19 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 84)
  - The SUNYA- ASRC Aerosol Detector- V.A Mohnen & P. Holtz, 1968 October (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 85)
  - An Experiment Illustrating that Gas Conversion by Solar Radiarion is a Major Influence in the Diurnal Variations of Aitken Nucleus Concentrations - Austin W. Hogan, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 86)
  - Photograph of a Close Lightning Flash - Richard E. Orville, 1968 November 8 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 87)
  - Application of an Inert Trcer to an AgI Seeding Experiment- A.W. Hogan, 1969 February (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 88)
  - Atmospheric Event- Lightning- Bernard Vonnegut, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 90)
  - Vegetation- Environment & Relations - J. Gary Holway & Jon T. Scott, 1969 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 92)
  - The Inadvertent Modification of the atmosphere by Air Pollution -V.J. Schaefer, 1969 April (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 93)
  - Some Effects of Air Pollution on Our Environment - V.J. Schaefer, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 94)
  - Wave Interaction & Langmuir Circulations- R. Stwert & R.K. Schmitt, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 96)
  - Procedings of the Ninth Annual Meeting of the New York- New Jersey Division Association of American Geographers, 1969 May (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 97)
  - On the Mechansim of Langmuir Circulations & their role in Epilimnion Mixing, 1969 July (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 98)
  - Thermal Discharge from Nuclear Plants & Related Wheather Modification- Ronald Stewart, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 99)
  - Initial Periodicity of New Geyser, Yellowstone National Park - W. Dort Jr., A.W. Hogan, and G.W. Reynolds Jr., 1969 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 100)
  - Adirondack Conference on Electrostatics- A.D. Moore & B. Vonnegut, 1969 September (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 101)
  - Conference Summery- Adirondack Conference on Electrostatics- B. Vonnegut, 1969 June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 102)
  - How Weather is Made: From a field station on Whiteface Mountain- R.E. Falconer, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 103)
  - Electrical Discharge from & between Clouds of Charged Aerosols- E. Barreto, 1969 December 20 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 104)
  - Ice, Snow, and Hot Water- R. Stewart, 1970 February 12 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 105)
  - Public Hearing on Atomic Energy Plants & Their Effects on the Environment- R. Stewart, 1970 February 6 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 106)
  - Interim Report- Tenth Field Research Expedition Northern Arizona, 1970 December 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 107)
  - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 108)
  - Escape from Pollution- The Adirondacks- V.J. Schaefer, 1970 Feburary-March (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 109)
  - Preliminary Results on the Formation of Negative Small Ions in the Trosphere- V.A. Mohnen, 1970 March 20 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 110)
  - Application of Recent Innovations in Ice Crystal Replication to the Study of PbI2 Nuclei- A.W. Hogen & R.J. Cheng, 1970 April 6-9 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 111)
  - A Call for Action- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 112)
  - Fog & Haze Facility- Final Report- J.E. Jiusto & V.J. Schaefer, 1970 May (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 113)
  - Weather Modification- J.E. Jiusto, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 114)
  - Great Lakes Snowstorms- Part 1 Cloud Physics, Aspects- J.E. Juisto & E.W. Holroyd III, 1970 August 12 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 115)
  - Great Lakes Snowstorms- Part 2 Synoptic & Climatological Aspects- J.E. Juisto, D.A. Paine, and M.L. Kaplan, 1970 May (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 116)
  - Lightning Spectroscopy- Photographic Techniques- R.E. Orivlle & L.E. Saloneve, 1970 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 117)
  - Generation of Mirco-Droplets by Freezing a Supercold Water Drop- R.J. Cheng, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 118)
  - Time Lapse Photography of Clouds- V.J. Schaefer, 1970 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 120)
  - Auto Exchaust, Pollution & Weather Patterns- V.J. Schaefer, 1970 October (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 121)
  - Final Report- Cooperative Oceanic Environment Study, 1968 June 8/August 27 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 122)
  - Third Annual Report to Air Resources Division, 1970 March 31 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 119)
  - Annual Report 1970- ASRC (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 123)
  - Hoarfrost & Rime- Raymond Falconer, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 124)
  - Lenticular Clouds- Raymond Falconer, 1970 Spring (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 125)
  - What Makes the leaves Change Color?- Raymond Falconer, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 126)
  - Air Pollution & the Temperature Inversion, 1970 October-November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 127)
  - 5,000 Join in Air Pollution Survey - V.A. Mohnen, 1970 August -September (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 128)
  - Condensation Nuclei: Production of Very Large Numbers in Country Air- V.J. Schaefer, 1970 November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 129)
  - Water Drop Freezing: Ejection of Microdroplets- R.J. Cheng, 1970 December (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 130)
  - Mircoscopic Study of Lead Iodide- Nucleated Ice Crystals- R.J. Cheng & A.W. Hogen, 1970 October (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 131)
  - You Can Sample The Air Around You- A. Hulstrunk, 1970 August- September (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 132)
  - Air Pollution and the Temperature Inversion- J.A. Weeks, 1970 October- November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 133)
  - Mechanism for the Water-to-Air Transfer & Concentration of Bacteria- D.C. Blenchard & L. Syzdek, 1970 November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 134)
  - The Threat of the Unseen- V.J. Schaefer, 1971 February 6 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 135)
  - Particle Production by Polymer Pyrolysis: Effect of Carbon Monoxide- V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 136)
  - Whiteface Weather Watchers- G. Killer, 1971 Spring (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 137)
  - Interim Report- Second Northern Arizona Field Research Expedition, 1970 December 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 138)
  - Simplified Airborne Solid Sampling, 1971 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 139)
  - Interim Report- Tenth Field Research Expedition to Yellowstone, 1970 May 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 140)
  - Final Report- Eleventh Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1971 May 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 141)
  - Lake Effect Storm Study- V.J. Schaefer, 1971 February (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 142)
  - The Atmosphere as a Science Classroom Resource- T.W. Norton, 1971 May (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 143)
  - Structure & Mechanism of Langmuir Circulations on a Small Inland Lake- G.E. Myer, 1971 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 144)
  - Relationship of Cloud Nuclei Spectra to Aerosol size Distribution & Composition- C. Junge & E. McLaren, 1971 April (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 145)
  - A Heated Thermistor System for Measuring Small Currents in Lakes- F.E. Tallman, 1971 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 146)
  - Physical A Studies on Lake George & Lake Ontario- J.T. Scott & R. Stewart, 1971 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 147)
  - Comperative Measurements with the ASRC Aerosol Detector- T.W. Norton, 1969 December 16 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 148)
  - Aquatic Plants in the Southern Basin of Lake George- M.W. Fenlon & S.W. Traver, 1971 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 149)
  - Wetlands- Capital District- M. Bonchonsky, 1970 October 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 150)
  - Evaluation of a Silicone Adhesive as an Aerosol Collecting Medium- A.W. Hogen, 1971 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 151)
  - The Production of Ice Crystal Fragments by Sublimation & Electrification - V.J. Schaefer & R.J. Cheng, 1971 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 152)
  - Electrically Produced Submicroscopic Aerosols- E. Barreto, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 153)
  - Airborne & Ground Measurement of the Atmospheric Potential Gradient a Solar Eclipse- R. Markson & A.K. Kamra, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 154)
  - Fourth Annual Report- ASRC, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 155)
  - Comphrensive Study of Maritime Aerosols- A.W. Hogen & M.H. Degeni, 1971 August 5 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 156)
  - Umschau- Kurzberichte, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 157)
  - Annual Report 1971- ASRC (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 158)
  - Meso- And Microscale Structure of Great Lakes Snowstorm Bands- E.W. Holroyod III, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 162)
  - The Mini- Events of the Weather- R.J. Cheng, 1971 August (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 163)
  - Contributions to the International Biological Program- R. Stewart, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 164)
  - Non- Photochemical Aersol Formation from the Anhydrous Reaction between Ammonia And Sulfer Dioxide Gases- V.A Mohnen, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 165)
  - Weather Modification Tehcnology Assessment- 1985 Projection- J.E. Juisto, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 166)
  - Crystal Development & Glaciation of a Supercooled Cloud- J.E. Juisto, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 167)
  - Air Quality of American Homes- V.J. Schaefer, V.A. Mohnen, and V.R. Veirs, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 168)
  - Snowmelt Delay by Oversnow Travel- A.W. Hogen, 1972 February (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 169)
  - Studies of Great Lakes Snowstorms- Collection of reprints, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 170)
  - The Borderland of Burning Bubbles- D.C. Blanchard, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 171)
  - The Oil Tanker & The Charged Mist- E. Barreto, 1972 April 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 172)
  - Falt Velocity of Snowflakes- J.E. Jiusto + G.E. Bosworth, 1971 December (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 173)
  - The Micro-World of Accidental Weather, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 174)
  - Microdroplets & Water Drop Freezing, 1971 August (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 175)
  - S'il Pleut C'est la Faute Aux Voitures!, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 176)
  - Snowfall from Lake-Effect Storms- J.E. Jiusto & M.L. Kaplan, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 177)
  - Snowfall from a Heavy Seeded Cloud- E.W. Holroyd & J.E. Juisto, 1971 April 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 178)
  - Satellite Monitoring of Black Bear, 1971 December 15 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 179)
  - "Atmospheric Electricity" - B. Vonnegut, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 181)
  - "Tornado"- B.Vonnegut, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 182)
  - Discussion of Paper by W.H.Evans, 'Electric Fields & Conductivity in Thunderclouds'- B. Vonnegut, 1969 December (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 183)
  - The Design, Construction, and Use of an Ice Crystal Counter for Ice Crystal Cloud Studies by Aircraft- J.D. McTaggart-Cowan, G.G. Lala, and B. Vonnegut, 1970 April (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 184)
  - Miniative Whrilwinds Produced in the laboratory by High-Voltage Electrical Discharges- R.T. Ryan & B. Vonnegut, 1970 April (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 185)
  - Eyewitness Tornado Oberservations Obtained with Telphone & Tape Recorder- R.T. Ryan & B. Vonnegut, 1970 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 186)
  - Time Lapse Photography of Clouds from High Altitude Balloons- B. Vonnegut, 1970 August (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 187)
  - A Laboratory Investigation of the Effect of Particle Collisions on the Generation of Electric Fileds In Thunderstorms- A.Karma & B. Vonnegut, 1971 May (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 188)
  - Meteorological Phenominon called Crown Flash - M.E. Greves, J.C. Gall Jr., 1971 May 28 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 189)
  - Lattice Spacing of Pseudobinary Solid Soultions of Silver Bromide & Silver Iodide- H. Chessin & B. Vonnegut, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 190)
  - Formation of a Vortex by an Elevated Heat Source, 1971 October 18 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 191)
  - Ice Nucleation by Coprecipitated Silver Iodide and Silver Bromide, 1971 November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 192)
  - Understanding Lightning- B. Vonnegut, 1971 December (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 193)
  - Early Experiments Seeding Cumulus with Agl, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 194)
  - Tornados im Labor- B. Vonnegut & R.T. Ryan, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 195)
  - Ion Annihilation by Aerosol Particles from Ground Level to 60km Height- J. Zikmunda & V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 196)
  - Climatic Modification Utilizing the Thermal Discharge from an Eletricity Generating Station- R. Stewart & J. Droppo, 1972 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 197)
  - Radiotracking of Grizzly Bears in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 194- F.C. Craighead Jr. & J.J. Craighead, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 198)
  - The Oceanic Production of Volatile Cloud Nuclei- D.C. Blandchard, 1970 October (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 199)
  - Adirondack Life- Raymond Falconer, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 200)
  - The Ways of the Wind- R.E. Falconer, 1972 January (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 201)
  - An Air Pollution Resource Manual For Junior High School & High School Teachers- R.G. Nurnberger, 1971 August (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 202)
  - Negative Ions in Air Like Gas Mixtures- V.A. Mohnen, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 203)
  - Interim Report- Ion Molecule Reactions of Atmospheric Importance- V.A. Mohnen, 1972 June 30 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 204)
  - Date On Grizzly Bear Denning Activites obtained by using Wildlife Telemetry- F.C. Craighead Jr. & J.J. Craighead, 1970 November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 206)
  - Laboratory Evaluation of an Electrogasdynamic Fog Dispersal Concept-J.C. Juisto, 1972 August (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 207)
  - Numerical Estimates of Humidity in a Membrane- Filter Ice Nucleus Chamber- G.G. Lala & J.E. Jiusto, 1972 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 208)
  - Age Determination of Grizzly Bears from Fourth Premolar Tooth Sections- J.J. Craighead & F.C. Craighead Jr., and H.E. McCutchen, 1970 April (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 209)
  - The Ecology of Raptor Predation, 1950 March (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 210)
  - National Geograpic- Trailing Yellowing's Grizzlies by Radio- F. Craighead Jr. & J. Craighead, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 212)
  - Exotic Big Game on Public Lands- F.C. Craighead Jr. & R.F. Craighead, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 213)
  - Grizzly Bear- Man Realtionship in Yellowstone National Park- J.J. Craighead & F.C. Craighead, 1971 August 15 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 214)
  - Grizzly Bear Prehibernation And Denning Activities as Determined by Radiotracking- J.J. Craighead & F.C. Craighead, 1972 November (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 215)
  - Satellite & Ground Radioactivity of ELK- F.C. Craighead Jr., J.J. Craighead, C.E. Cote, and H.K. Buechner, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 218)
  - Contributions to the International Biological Program - R. Stewart Year II, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 219)
  - Study of Maritime Aerosols- A.W. Hogen & M.H. Degani, 1972 September 1 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 220)
  - Concentration of Bacteria in Jet Drops from Bursting Bubbles- D.C. Blanchard & L.D. Syzdek, 1972 September 20 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 221)
  - ASRC Report 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 222)
  - A Nummerical & Experimental Study of Humidity in a Membrane Filter Ice Nucleus Chamber- G.G. Lala, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 223)
  - A Proposed Size Distribution Function for Natural Aerosols- T.A. Rich & V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 225)
  - Studying Wildlife by Satellite- F.C. Craighead Jr. & J.J. Craighead, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 226)
  - Electrostatics Selected Classified Bibliography, 1973 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 228)
  - A Change in the Weather - A.W. Hogen & R.E. Falconer, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 229)
  - Life on the Summit- Red Buck, 1973 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 230)
  - Artifical Growth of "Icicle" Lobe Structure of a Hailstorm in a Wind Tunnel- N.R. Gokhale & J.D. Spengler, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 232)
  - Wilson Bentley, Pioneer in Snowflake Photomicrography- D.C. Blanchard, 1973 May (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 236)
  - Numerical Estimates of Humidity in a Membrane- Filter Ice Nucleus Chamber- G.G. Lala & J.E. Jiusto, 1972 June (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 237)
  - An Underground Electronic Field Meter- R.A. Cudney, C.T. Phelps, and E. Barreto, 1972 September (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 238)
  - Radiotracking of Grizzly Bears & ELK in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1966 - F.C. Craighead Jr. & J.J. Craighead, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 241)
  - Biotelemetry Research with Grizzly Bears & Elk in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming 1965- F.C. Craighead Jr., 1971 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 242)
  - Radiotracking of Grizzly Bears- F.C. Craighead Jr., J.J. Craighead, and R.S. Davies, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 243)
  - A Biological & Economic Evaluation of Coyote Preadation- F.C. Craighead Jr., 1957 July (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 244)
  - A tracking & Telemetry System for Wildlife Research- J.R. Varney, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 245)
  - Development of Satellite- Related Biometelemetry- J.J. Craighead, F.C. Craighead Jr., and J.R. Varney, 1971 July 31 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 246)
  - Reproductive Biology of Young Female Grizzly Bears- J.J. Craighead, M.G. Hornocker, and F.C. Craighead Jr., 1969 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 247)
  - Tuning in on the Grizzly- F.C. Craighead and J.J Craighead, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 249)
  - Satellites for Research on Free- Roaming Animals- H.K. Buechner, F.C. Craighead, and C.E. Cote, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 250)
  - Whitewater Adventure on Wild Rivers of Idaho- J.J. Craighead & F.C. Craighead Jr., 1970 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 251)
  - Fine Particle Measurements in the Air Over the North Atlantic Ocean- V.J. Schaefer, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 253)
  - Photomicroscopical Investigation of the Fragmentation of Hydrometeors in the Laboratory- R.J. Cheng, 1973 July/October (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 264)
  - Hail-R.E. Falconer, 1973 June/July (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 265)
  - The Mechinism of multiplication Process of Glaciation in the Atmosphere- R.J. Cheng, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 266)
  - Radiotracking of Grizzly Bears in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming- F.C. Craighead Jr, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 267)
  - Simplified Experiments in Atmospheric Physics- V.J. Schafer, 1955 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 268)
  - Continous Cloud Chamber for Studying Small Particles in the Atmosphere- V.J. Schaefer, 1952 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 269)
  - Formation of Ice Crystals in Ordinary and Nuclei-Free Air- V.J. Schaefer, 1952 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 270)
  - Effect of Electric Field on Charge Separation by the falling Precipitation Mechanism in Thunderclouds-A.K. Karma, 1970 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 271)
  - Meteorological Effects of Spray Cooling in the Great Lakes Climate- R.Stewart, U. Czapski, and R.T. Nelson, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 272)
  - Electrostatics and It's Applications- A.D. Moore, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 273)
  - Snowfall Studies- Final Report NoAA Grant 04-3-022-17- J.E. Jiusto, 1973 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 274)
  - Electrostatics Selected Classified Bibliography- Volume II, 1974 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 275)
  - They're Kilining Yellowstone Grizlies- F.C. Craighead Jr., Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 276)
  - Comments on "Oceanic Areosol Levels Deduced from Measurements of the Electrical Conductivity of the Atomsphere"- A.W. Hogan, V.A. Mohnen, and V.J. Schaefer, 1973 October (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 277)
  - Drift- Man-Made and Natural-R.T. Nelson, B. Vicki, T. Jursak, R. Stewart, 1974 January (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 280)
  - Types of Snowfall- J.E. Jiusto and H.K. Weikmann, 1973 November (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 282)
  - Remote Detection of Thermals by means of horizontal Electric Field Measurements- R. Markson, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 284)
  - Atmosphere Electrical Detection of Organized Convenction- R. Markson, 1975 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 287)
  - A New look at Electrostatic Air Cleaners- D.L. Mc.Clenahan, 1974 October (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 288)
  - Two Examples of Fasciation in Northern Arizona-V.J. Schaefer, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 292)
  - The Mechinism of multiplication Process of Glaciation in the Atmosphere- R.J. Cheng, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 293)
  - Thermal Discharge: Use It- R.Stewart, S.P. Mathur, L.J. Vicki, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 294)
  - Reply- J.E. Jiusto and G.G LaLa, 1972 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 298)
  - Remarks on Ice Nucleation Mechanisms in Clouds- J.E. Jiusto, 1973 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 299)
  - Seeding Requirements for Rapid Glaciation or Stimulation of a Mixed Phase Cloud- J.E. Juisto, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 300)
  - Wilson Bentley, the Snowflake Man, 1970 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 302)
  - A Single Method for the Production of Water Drops in the Range of 6mm to 10mm Diameter- D.C. Blanchard, 1971 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 303)
  - Whitecaps at Sea- D.C. Blandchard, 1971 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 304)
  - How to Tell the Truths- D.C. Blanchard, 1971 March (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 305)
  - Variations in Aitken & Giant Nuclei in Marine Air- D.C. Blanchard & L. Syzdek, 1972 July (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 306)
  - Bentley & Lenard: Pioneers in Cloud Physics- D.C. Blanchard, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 307)
  - Drop-Size Distributions Produced by the Breakup of Large Drops Under Turbulence- A.J. Ausa & D.C. Blanchard, 1973 January (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 308)
  - Comments on "Formation of a Rain A Shower by Salt Seeding- D.C. Blanchard, 1971 September 21 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 310)
  - Surface Water D.C. Blanchard, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 311)
  - From Raindrops to Volcanoes- D.C. Blanchard, 1967 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 312)
  - Heteromolecular Nucleation Theory Applied to Gas-to-Particle Conversion- C.S. Kieng, D. Staufer, V.A. Mohnen, J.Bricard, and D. Vigla, 1973 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 314)